

# Nicole Forbes

## Professional summary

Hardworking and passionate professional with two years experience in front-end development eager to secure entry-level front-end developer position. Dependable, and successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals and thrives working on challenging projects with diverse personalities.

## Work history

## Discovery Academy - Teaching Assistant

08/2021 - 12/2021

- Responsible for supporting the teaching and learning in a class of 9 students with Special Education Needs and Disabilities, working alongside a class teacher and a HLTA.
- Working closely with internal and external stakeholders to successfully contribute to the delivery of the vision, ethos, aims and objectives of the academy.
- Caring passionately about each child as an individual, and being able to observe and listen and then respond to advice.
- Tutored struggling students individually and in small groups to reinforce learning concepts.

#### LV - Customer Service Representative

10/2020 - 08/2021

- Resolving customer queries and issues by phone, consistently meeting and exceeding KPIs, and achieving customer satisfaction ratings of 97% upwards.
- Using strong written communication skills and attention to detail to write letters to customers, update customer files, and provide feedback to management using in-house systems and software.
- Building rapport by effectively liaising and working with internal departments in order to help solve customer issues.
- Maintained up-to-date knowledge of product and service changes.
- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Processed customer adjustments to maintain financial accounts.

#### Santander - Customer Service Advisor

10/2018 - 05/2019

- ➤ nforbes.dev@gmail.com
- 07534046251
- O CV7 8GH
- www.nicoleforbes.co.uk

#### Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Debugging
- Responsive design
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Problem Solving
- Organization

#### **Education**

12/2022 - Current

Meta

Programming with Javascript

05/2022

### **Bath Spa University**

Web Development

2016

#### **Leeds Beckett University**

Certificate in Foundation Language Studies: Japanese

2013

## University of Sheffield

BA History and Philosophy

2010

# **Huddersfield New College**

A Level

Classical Civilisations - A

- Demonstrated good attention to detail when dealing with customer accounts, including but not limited to, sending money on behalf of the customer, investigating for any signs of fraud, logging complaints and feedback, all using the company's in-house systems.
- Remaining calm under pressure while taking high volumes of inbound calls from customers, as well as working with other departments such as fraud and mortgages.
- Being an advocate for digital services, and coaching customers on how to install banking apps or use the website so they could easily take care of their own accounts online.
- Responded to customer needs through competent customer service and prompt problem-solving.

## ASDA - Hybrid Host

11/2013 - 08/2018

- Speedily helped customers who needed help on self-service checkouts to make their experience as easy as possible, all the while achieving a 100% customer satisfaction rating
- Frequently stepped up to help supervise the checkout department, and trained 8 co-workers on checkout and self-service.
- Worked with customers to understand needs and provide excellent service.
- Participated in continuous improvement by generating suggestions, engaging in problem-solving activities to support teamwork.

Medieval History – A Graphic Illustration – A